Anthony Bollas 1947 Churchill Drive Union, NJ 07083 (973) 687 6482 Anthonybollas@gmail.com

September 22, 2022

To whom it may concern,

I am very excited to apply for position at your establishment and ask that you allow me to represent your company as an IOS Engineer. I believe that my academic background alongside my dedication to learning and the soft skills I have developed during my employment with companies within the technology field make me an excellent candidate to represent you as an IOS engineer.

I have obtained an A.S. in Computer Science from Union County College, and will receive my B.S. in Computer Science from Kean University in 2024. During my time at these institutions, I attained an understanding of data structures, learned to interpret complex algorithms, worked with databases, experimented with web development, and was introduced to mobile development. I have also taken courses that develop my technical writing, public speaking, and research. All of these skills will allow me to be exceptional at producing IOS applications, assisting others, and presenting projects.

When I was newly exposed to the field of Computer Science, there were many topics I wanted to learn that my school did not provide. I then went onto the internet and used all sources that were accessible to me to expand my knowledge. I favored an app called Udemy that allowed me to improve my skill with python and further expose me to its libraries. After, I began an IOS development course in which I became more familiar with swift, SwiftUI, and XCode. I had become so passionate about swift that I decided it was what I wanted to master.

As I was an employee of BestBuy and Apple, I learned many soft skills to help me excel in my career. During my positions at both these companies, I learned to actively listen and adapt to clientele of all types and provided personalized solutions for everyone. I have assisted in situations where there has been a communication barrier such as language, or disabilities. Both the companies I worked for established all of their employees as a team, but also taught me about personal brand. Although our metrics are measured as a team, our personal brand is how we represent ourselves. When I began working for Apple, they were very prominent with feedback, and it was clear that teamwork and growth were to be taken very seriously. In addition to the soft skills, I became familiar with all the Apple products especially since I had to present and sell them to clientele as a solution.

Please allow me to interview as an IOS Engineer. Thank you for your time and consideration. If I have been considered for the position you can contact me at anthonybollas@gmail.com or (973)-687-6482.

Sincerely,

Anthony Bollas

Anthony Bollas

<u>Email</u>	<u>Phone</u>	<u>Address</u>	<u>URL</u>
Anthonybollas@gmail.com	(973)-687-6482	1947 Churchill Dr, Union, NJ, 07083	https://github.com/abollas99

Self-motivated Computer Science student at Kean University with Associates of Science from Union County College and 5 years of work experience in customer service, problem solving, organization, and teamwork. One year of experience diagnosing and repairing computers. Eager to learn using Udemy with a primary focus in IOS development. Proficient in Python, Java, HTML, CSS, Swift, and java script.

Education

UNION COUNTY COLLEGE GPA: 3.1

GFA. 3.1

Cranford, NJ

Associates of Science in Computer Science (Jan 2022)

Relevant Coursework

- Computer Algorithms
- Programming for Mobile Devices
- Intro to information Systems
- Intro to Operating Systems
- Linux Fundamentals
- System Analysis and Design
- Computer Organization, Architecture and Assembly Language
- Unified Calculus I

KEAN UNIVERSITY

GPA: 3.6

Union, NJ

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (Expected graduation May 2024)

Relevant Coursework

- Data Structures
- · Applied Statistics
- Analysis of Algorithms
- Technical Writing
- Public Speaking

Achievements

Dean's List

Experience

SPECIALIST

Apple Inc., Short hills, NJ / Jul 2022 - present

- Probe to discover what products can go well with the customers lifestyle
- Use the apple steps of service in every interaction
- Provide solutions for customers that come in with issues
- Support customers through the process of setting up their new devices
- Explain the features of all of our products to the customer
- Introduce and offer Apple as a business solution
- Offer our extended services to teach client how to use their new product

Organize customers and place them in a queue

GEEK SQUAD CONSULTATION AGENT

Best Buy, Union, NJ / Jul 2021 - Jul 2022

- Meet a sales goal for all services
- Diagnose customer devices ranging from computer to mobile phones
- Perform software repairs
- Inspected products and prepared to be resold
- · Prepare new agents to properly assist customers
- · Learn to adapt and figure out a solution for each customer
- Setup and prepare customers products for them to pickup

SALES CONSULTANT

Best Buy, Union, NJ / Sep 2018 - Jul 2021

- Provide a solution for the customer's needs
- Explore and build product knowledge in all departments
- · Adapt and produce a solution for customers even if a communication barrier exists
- · Perform as a team to reach communal goals as a store
- Mentor new hires and provide them with the knowledge needed to successfully assist customers
- Produce a sales tracker for leaders to evaluate sales daily

Skills

- Client Relations
- Problem Resolution
- Team Player
- MacOS Proficient
- Windows Proficient
- Linux Proficient
- Object Oriented Programming
- Data Structures
- Microsoft Office Proficient
- Git Proficient
- Technical Writing
- Adaptable
- Open to Feedback
- Good Listener

Programming Languages

- Python
 - Pandas
 - Tkinter
- Java
- HTML/CSS
 - Bootstrap
- Java Script
- Swift
 - SwiftUI
- Android Studio

Languages

- English
- Portuguese